

# Ashraf **JDI**

### Full-Stack web & hybrid mobile apps developer

Casablanca, Morocco	ttps://achrafjdily.github.io/me
achrafjdily@gmail.com	+212700258339
in in/achraf-jdily	<b> ● @</b> AchrafJdily
achrafjdily	© +212700258339 ~Achraf

### INTRODUCTION

I'm a software developer specialized & experienced in full-stack web & hybrid mobile apps development. I have acquired and developed many soft & hard skills over the course of 4 years of my professional career as well as my educational path, which makes me a great fit in many software engineering positions.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Promv

Full time - Remote

# September 2020 - July 2023 Full Stack web developer

Techs & Tools : 🕪 - PHP

🕼 - LARAVEL

JS - JAVASCRIPT

V - VUE

git - GIT

- GITLAB

- DOCKER

- Collaborated and built a real estate rentals platform that automates and eases the rental process with multiple features like generation of rental agreements, complex financial accounting and payments tracking. Led many architectural and engineering decisions throughout the project
- Collaborated in the development of a Saas platform providing multiple services to real estate developers. Helped with system design and code refactoring. Solely developed and led severals decisions in some parts of the platform and its subprojects and features like making of financial balance sheet auto calculator by implementing complex calculations in user-friendly spreadsheet-like interfaces. Contributed on the development of other complex and advanced features such as multi-layered maps with some 3d layers.
- Analysed requirements, wrote tasks and issues and actively helped manage and estimate the projects.
- Helped deploy and monitor several apps and websites and intervened with hotfixes and QFE update even in off-work hours.
- Helped and Contributed on the making of user-friendly UX/UI designs, and interactive tutorials for the company apps.
- Closely worked with the project manager and the product owner

January 2023 - April 2023

### **Immofind**

Part time - Remote

# Full Stack web developer

Techs & Tools: PHP

P - LARAVEL

JS - JAVASCRIPT

- ALPINEJS

git - GIT

- GITLAB

- DOCKER

- Built a real estate search and matching platform to ease & simplify real estate searching for end-users.
- Implemented advanced filtering & accurate suggesting systems by utilizing matching calculations based on user-intered data.
- Refactored the existing code and built end-users and admin panels UI.
- Analysed requirements, prioritized tasks and milestones, mentored & helped team members to use project management tools.
- Setup linux server, deployed the platform, managed and monitored the software and hardware required infrastructure.

April 2021 - August 2021

### Moenn

Part time - Remote

# **Lead Angular Frontend developer**

Techs & Tools: TS - TYPESCRIPT A - ANGULAR git - GIT

- GITLAB

- Laid the architecture and foundation of frontend apps including main features.
- Helped and mentored trainees about Angular, Rxjs and Ngrx with redux patterns.
- Coordinated work of front-end and back-end dev teams

August 2019 - June 2020

#### **Devaxy**

Full time - Onsite

# Full Stack web developer

Techs & Tools : 🙉 - PHP

🕼 - LARAVEL

TS - TYPESCRIPT

A - ANGULAR

• IONIC

git - GIT

C - GITHUB

- Laid the architecture and foundation of frontend and hybrid mobile apps.
- Created Frontend admin app as well as multiple responsive web apps for the clients and end-users.
- Created two cross-platform mobile apps (in Ionic Framework for Android and iOS).
- Helped and mentored team members about Angular and Typescript.
- Engaged in research and development to find the best tools and solutions for several use cases.
- Collaborated with the UI/UX design team to make good looking and user-friendly UI interfaces.

### **EDUCATION**

September 2019 - July 2020 O Professional bachelor's degree: **Database administration & Web** technologies

Faculty of Science and Technology -

September 2017 - July 2019 Specialized technician's degree : multimedia & web development OFPPT - SIAT NICT SIDI MAÂROUF 2

June 2015 - September 2023

**Baccalaureate in physical sciences** Lycée al-Mokhtar Soussi

### **TECH STACK**

Backend: PHP

🕼 - LARAVEL

- REST APIS - MICROSERVICES

Frontend: JS - JAVASCRIPT TS - TYPESCRIPT A - ANGULAR O - NGRX

V - VUE

→ - ALPINEJS ~ TAILWIND CSS

Other tools: git - GIT

- DOCKER

- GITLAB

C - GITHUB

### LANGUAGES

 English: Professional & fluent usage • French: Professional & fluent usage

Arabic: First language

# **SOFT SKILLS**

- Problem solving
- Teamwork
- Attention to details and requirements
- Work ethics
- Adaptability
- Communication
- Autonomy